Carroll Vance

cs.vance AT icloud.com

Portfolio: https://csvance.github.io Github: https://github.com/csvance

Profile

I am an undergraduate student studying Computer Science at the University of Houston. I have professional experience working with embedded systems for a variety of applications including robotics/automation, networking, and storage.

Skills

Developed applications for embedded micro controllers and microprocessors such as PIC, ARM Cortex M0, M3, M4, A7, A57 and more. Extensive experience with embedded Linux ranging from board bringup to custom distribution creation with Yocto Project. Familiar with a large variety of buses, sensors, and actuators. Proficient in C/C++/Python. ROS. Embedded machine learning inference optimization.

Education

UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON – 2018-CURRENT

Expected Graduation: Fall 2020 with B.S. in Computer Science & Minor in Mathematics

HOUSTON COMMUNITY COLLEGE - 2016-2018

Studied Computer Science

CUMULATIVE GPA - 4.0

Experience

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, WILDCAT DEVELOPMENT; SPRING, TEXAS – 2009-2016

Designed and implemented embedded software for micro controllers and microprocessors for companies such as Baker Hughes, Hewlett Packard Enterprise, and National Oilwell Varco

SYSTEMS VALIDATION TESTER, WAILUA TECHNOLOGY; HOUSTON, TEXAS – 2008-2009Executed test plan for flash memory technology created by Spansion and Virident Systems

Extracurricular

CULLEN COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING IEEE – MAKERSPACE OFFICER, 2018-CURRENT DATA ANALYTICS IN STUDENT HANDS - MEMBER, 2018-CURRENT